[
  {
    "question": "Who can we thank for creating Calvin and Hobbes?",
    "options": ["Bill Watterson", "Charles Schulz", "Stan Lee", "Frank Miller"],
    "answer": "Bill Watterson"
  },

  {
    "question": "How did he come up with the name Hobbes?",
    "options": [
      "It was the name of his own childhood cat",
      "He was named after Thomas Hobbes, a 17th century philosopher",
      "He was named after the mayor of his hometown where he grew up",
      "He used a rap name generator"
    ],
    "answer": "He was named after Thomas Hobbes, a 17th century philosopher"
  },

  {
    "question": "in Calvin and Hobbes' secret club G.R.O.S.S. what does this acronym stand for?",
    "options": ["Grownups R Overly Suppressive Slugs", "Girls R Oh So Silly", "Get Rid Of Slimy Susie", "Get Rid Of Slimy GirlS"],
    "answer": "Get Rid Of Slimy GirlS"
  },

  {
    "question": "What is Calvin's favorite costume that his mother made for him?",
    "options": ["Spaceman Spiff", "Tracer Bullet", "Stupendous Man", "Batman"],
    "answer": "Stupendous Man"
  },

  {
    "question": "The Transmogrifier, Time Machine, and Duplicator are all the same of what object?",
    "options": ["Trash can", "Blanket fort", "Large white sheet", "Large box"],
    "answer": "Large box"
  },

  {
    "question": "What does the Tansmogrifier do?",
    "options": [
      "Changes Calvin into any form of Play-Doh",
      "Changes Calvin into different animals",
      "Transforms Calvin into his Dad’s physical appearance",
      "Transforms Hobbes into another Calvin"
    ],
    "answer": "Changes Calvin into different animals"
  },

  {
    "question": "What was the name of Calvin and Hobbes' favorite game where you can’t use the same rules twice?",
    "options": ["Crazyball", "Calvinball", "Hobbescotch", "Calvinclues"],
    "answer": "Calvinball"
  },

  {
    "question": "Who was Calvin's babysitter?",
    "options": ["Margery", "Candice", "Rosalyn", "Kathy"],
    "answer": "Rosalyn"
  },

  {
    "question": "What is the name of Calvin's teacher?",
    "options": ["Mrs. Treebottom", "Mrs. Wormwood", "Mr. Hemlock", "Mrs. Ploomsey"],
    "answer": "Mrs. Wormwood"
  },

  {
    "question": "From what years was “Calvin and Hobbes” syndicated?",
    "options": ["1980 - 1985", "1985 - 1995", "1983 - 1993", "1987 - 1999"],
    "answer": "1985 - 1995"
  },

  {
    "question": "Out of the following comics, which one did not inspire the author to write 'Calvin and Hobbes'?",
    "options": ["Peanuts", "Krazy Kat", "Pogo", "Garfield"],
    "answer": "Peanuts"
  },

  {
    "question": "Who is Calvin named after?",
    "options": ["The Author's Brother", "A sixteenth-century theologian", "The Author's Cat", "The Author's Dad"],
    "answer": "A sixteenth-century theologian"
  },

  {
    "question": "What are the names of Calvin's parents?",
    "options": ["Sue and Jasper", "Their names were never mentioned", "Wanda and Darryl", "Andy and Roger"],
    "answer": "Their names were never mentioned"
  },

  {
    "question": "Where did Susie Derkins' last name come from?",
    "options": [
      "The author's best friend",
      "The author's cat",
      "The author's nickname in high school",
      "The nickname of the author's wife's family dog"
    ],
    "answer": "The nickname of the author's wife's family dog"
  },

  {
    "question": "Who is Moe?",
    "options": ["Calvin's cousin", "Calvin's best friend", "A bully at Calvin's school", "Calvin's babysitter"],
    "answer": "A bully at Calvin's school"
  },

  {
    "question": "In the first \"Calvin and Hobbes\" strip, what kind of bait did Calvin put in his trap?",
    "options": ["Worms", "A carrot", "A tuna fish sandwich", "A bowl of chowder"],
    "answer": "A tuna fish sandwich"
  },

  {
    "question": "When Calvin duplicated himself the first time, how many Calvins, including the original, were there altogether?",
    "options": ["6", "5", "3", "62"],
    "answer": "6"
  },

  {
    "question": "When Calvin duplicated himself the first time, what did he end up turning all his duplicates into?",
    "options": ["A bowl of chowder", "Worms", "Peanuts", "Rocks"],
    "answer": "Worms"
  },

  {
    "question": "How long in advanced do Sunday strips have to be drawn to get color plates?",
    "options": ["2 months", "2 days", "2 weeks", "6 weeks"],
    "answer": "2 months"
  },

  {
    "question": "What planet did Susie and Calvin get assigned to research?",
    "options": ["Saturn", "Mars", "Mercury", "Jupiter"],
    "answer": "Mercury"
  }
]
